intango.com 2018-07-06

# Privacy Policy - Intango

Welcome to Intango.com (“Intango”, “we”, “us” or “Site”). We are committed to maintain the privacy of its customers. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices.

Information we collect

Intango Ltd. Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) explains the types of information that we gather and what we do with it. In our registration process, as either a “Publisher” or “Advertiser” on Intango’s Performance Network (“RevenueHis”) we ask users to provide contact information, for example, your company name, billing information and email address. We may also request a unique login password, and confirmation that you have accepted our terms and conditions of use and wish to receive our monthly newsletter. If required to complete a transaction, we might also request financial information including PayPal account or credit card numbers. You may modify the information you have provided at any time from within your personal control panel.

We use customer contact information to provide services and occasionally, provide information on our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. We use unique identifiers, such as login & password, to verify the user’s identity and as account numbers in our customer database system. We also use information in the aggregate to demonstrate, for example, the number of people registered with the company. Unless required to complete a transaction you have requested, or to perform maintenance on our site, we do not share personal identifying information with outside entities.

We use “cookies” on our site to remember you and ensure you do not view the same ads repeatedly. We also use cookies to estimate the number of unique visitors to the site and provide aggregate information about our user base. However, we do not associate our members with cookies, the member remains anonymous.

In addition, our member’s advertisements may contain cookies. While we use cookies in certain sections of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by the advertising company and we do not have access to this information. You may delete the cookies on your machine by following the instructions provided with your Internet browser software.

Information Sharing

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information: (a) As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process. (b) When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. (c)If My Private Search is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our extension of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. (d) To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Use of Information

We may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to: (a) Manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support. (b) Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others. (c) Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties. (d) Cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings. (e) Manage our business.

Opt out

Intango respects your privacy. If you do not wish to reset your setting(s), you can decline/opt-out of the setting(s) change by deleting them under the instructions of your browser (“Help” section).

Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Access to Personally Information is strictly limited, and we take massive measures to ensure that Personally Information is not accessible to the public. All of our users’ Personally Information is restricted in our offices. If you have any questions about security on our extension, you can contact us.

Minors

Intango platforms are not designated for minors under the age of 13. In addition, we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will take all appropriate steps in order to remove such information from Intango records.

Updates

From time to time we might make some changes to our privacy policy. In that case we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Contact us

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: media@intango.com

By registering with Intango Ltd you agree to have your company logo, creative and other non-confidential collateral displayed on our site or in press releases and other print materials. This information can be removed upon your request.

Last Updated: June, 2018
